



I've always had a strong passion for the web. Shortly after I was given my first computer, I grew interested in web development. I take pride in writing maintainable and efficient code and have always enjoyed the feeling of accomplishment when programming. I not only take pride in my own work, but I genuinely care that the team I'm a part of succeeds in delivering great products that offer an excellent user experience. I'm also constantly furthering my skills by learning new patterns, libraries, and frameworks to keep up with the ever changing demand the web has.

# Job Experience

#### **CDIT**

Senior Frontend Engineer

December 2020 - Present

Built and architected a new mobile first dashboard, membership cart, and a live instructor-guided online education platform for dentists and their practices using Vue 3, TypeScript, Nuxt, and GraphQL.

Helped build a new platform in React for a VOIP client and migrated modules from NPM packages to Webpack Module Federation to allow for a better Micro Frontend architecture.

### Veriforce

Senior Frontend Engineer

July 2017 - December 2020

Architected applications in React, Redux, TypeScript, and Material-UI and wrote unit tests with Jest and React Testing Library for a contractor management platform.

Led a team of developers that met client deadlines for major revenue growing projects.

Mentored teammates by having pair programming sessions and provided feedback on code reviews daily.

Advocated for UI and code consistency throughout the application by creating patterns for other teammates to follow.

Set up a monorepo using Lerna for over a dozen React applications and NPM packages saving hours from weekly manual deployments.

Quarterly managed dependency upgrades that fixed underlying bugs and allowed developers to use new features.

Migrated existing React applications to TypeScript to reduce bugs and provide a better developer experience.

#### Netchex

**Full Stack Software Developer** 

November 2014 - July 2017

Worked in an agile environment on an application that specialized in payroll, benefits, and human resources.

Led a team of developers on a rewrite of the benefits module.

Developed applications using domain driven design with C# for REST APIs and created single page applications using AngularJS, TypeScript, and Bootstrap.

## **Skills**

















## Education

### **Nicholls State University**

Bachelor of Science (B.S.)

August 2009 - December 2013



Majored in Computer Information Systems

GPA: 3.6

### **Awards**

Consistently been awarded the President's List award since the Fall 2010 semester. The President's List award requires a student to maintain a scholastic GPA of 3.5 or higher.

### **Organizations**

Member of Beta Gamma Sigma. It is the highest recognition a business student anywhere in the world can receive in a business program accredited by AACSB International.

Member of Upsilon Pi Epsilon. It is the first and only existing international honor society in the Computing and Information disciplines.